[
    {
        "question": "Which one must follow all public health and safety regulations to ensure the protection and well-being of patients?",
        "choices": ["All health care practitioners", "Client", "People", "Patient"],
        "answer": "All health care practitioners"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Health and Safety at Work Act number means that employers must, by law, provide a safe working environment for all members of the workforce, including those with disabilities using their premises?",
        "choices": ["Act of 1973", "Act of 1974", "Act of 1975", "Act of 1976"],
        "answer": "Act of 1974"
    },
    {
        "question": "What can you say about the guidelines to guarantee the safety of your clients?",
        "choices": [
            "Seldom wash hands thoroughly between clients and prior to resuming treatment.",
            "Wash all linens in soap and cold water. Store and transport them in a sanitary manner.",
            "Always thoroughly sterilize table, headrest, equipment, and other tools between clients.",
            "Donâ€™t know all local ordinances and health department regulations regarding the type of clinic you work in."
        ],
        "answer": "Always thoroughly sterilize table, headrest, equipment, and other tools between clients."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your opinion about an endangerment site?",
        "choices": [
            "These areas may contain bony projections that are fragile and may be broken.",
            "These areas are not well protected by muscle or connective tissue and have the potential to be damaged.",
            "Massage therapists should exercise extreme caution when working in or close to these endangerment areas.",
            "An endangerment site is a region of the body in which nerves, arteries, or veins lay close to the body's surface."
        ],
        "answer": "An endangerment site is a region of the body in which nerves, arteries, or veins lay close to the body's surface."
    },
    {
        "question": "In maintaining health and safety in their place of work, what must be the role of a therapist?",
        "choices": [
            "Maintain the highest standards of personal and salon hygiene.",
            "Do not ignore any hazard or risk; make sure that corrective action is taken.",
            "Do not report faulty equipment to the person responsible for dealing with these issues.",
            "Do not keep a record of clients and report any problems that you have identified and cured."
        ],
        "answer": "Maintain the highest standards of personal and salon hygiene."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why should you plug the machine into a near and accessible identified socket?",
        "choices": [
            "It can be disconnected easily in an emergency.",
            "It will lessen your time from walking if you unplug it.",
            "It is easy for you to just reach out to unplug it.",
            "You can sleep anytime you want, and it is safe."
        ],
        "answer": "It can be disconnected easily in an emergency."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why should you follow the correct procedures when using electrical equipment?",
        "choices": [
            "To avoid accidents",
            "To show your expertise",
            "To play safely",
            "To boost your capacity to operate the equipment."
        ],
        "answer": "To avoid accidents"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call the type of drape used to protect the client's hair?",
        "choices": ["Turban drape", "Gluteal drape", "Breast drape", "Facial drape"],
        "answer": "Turban drape"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the technique of using a large towel or sheet to keep you covered while getting a massage?",
        "choices": ["Bathing", "Cleaning", "Draping", "Massaging"],
        "answer": "Draping"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following strokes of friction is also known as the heat rub?",
        "choices": ["Rolling", "Sawing", "Superficial warming", "Wringing"],
        "answer": "Superficial warming"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is an ancient healing practice that targets specific areas of your body by applying pressure to points on the hands?",
        "choices": ["Hand Massage", "Foot Reflexology", "Face Reflexology", "Hand Reflexology"],
        "answer": "Hand Reflexology"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary reason for cooking food?",
        "choices": ["Enhance taste", "Increase size", "Improve color", "Kill bacteria"],
        "answer": "Kill bacteria"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which cleaner is best for removing grease buildup?",
        "choices": ["Detergent", "Acid cleaner", "Abrasive cleaner", "Solvent cleaner"],
        "answer": "Solvent cleaner"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the proper storage method for cutting boards?",
        "choices": ["Store upright in a dry place", "Lay flat on the counter", "Hang with utensils", "Keep in a sealed container"],
        "answer": "Store upright in a dry place"
    },
    {
        "question": "What strokes in effleurage use the index and middle finger, held together or apart, thus forming a letter 'V' to glide toward one direction and check the proper alignment of muscles and spine?",
        "choices": ["Nerve stroke", "One-Handed Raking", "Two-Handed Circular", "Two-Handed Heart"],
        "answer": "One-Handed Raking"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which material is commonly used for baking dishes?",
        "choices": ["Aluminum", "Cast iron", "Ceramic", "Plastic"],
        "answer": "Ceramic"
    },
    {
        "question": "What method would be applied when we uncover the back and fold the drape down to the gluteal cleft?",
        "choices": ["Anterior Leg", "Gluteal Drape", "Posterior Leg", "Breast Drape"],
        "answer": "Gluteal Drape"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is an example of kitchen equipment?",
        "choices": ["Knife", "Spoon", "Fork", "Blender"],
        "answer": "Blender"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which table napkin fold resembles a boat?",
        "choices": ["Pyramid", "Candle", "Sailing Boat", "Fan"],
        "answer": "Sailing Boat"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary goal of sanitizing utensils?",
        "choices": ["Remove dirt", "Enhance durability", "Improve appearance", "Kill bacteria"],
        "answer": "Kill bacteria"
    }
]
